Contact

mmadihagull@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/madiha-gulb25a30108 (LinkedIn) github.com/MadihaGul (Portfolio)

Top Skills

Programming
Object-Oriented Programming
(OOP)
ASP.NET

Languages

Urdu (Native or Bilingual)
English (Professional Working)
Swedish (Limited Working)

Madiha Gul

.NET Developer | Seeker

Gothenburg, Vastra Gotaland County, Sweden

Summary

Computer Engineer with 4 years experience in C# .NET web-application development. Throughout my studies, I focused on IT and programming, working in a corporate environment enhanced my creativity as well as analytical and problem-solving skills. To improve my skillset, I studied .NET programming at Lexicon Göteborg and currently I am preparing for Azure certification. I am keen to learn new skills and focused to develop and maintain high-quality technical solutions. I desire to inspire and be inspired, achieve my goal of personal and professional improvement through challenges and experiences.

Experience

Yoin Technologies AB
Praktikant
April 2023 - Present (1 month)
Gothenburg, Vastra Gotaland County, Sweden

Army Welfare Trust Software Developer September 2014 - August 2018 (4 years) Northern Punjab Rawalpindi, Pakistan

In 2014, I joined AWT Realestate and contributed in the development of a web-based application which is currently being used by the company's head office and 3 site offices. I was handling the AWT realestate project under the supervision of AWT MIS department until August 2018, from taking the requirements in non technical language to the release incorporating the new features. During this tenure, I was mainly responsible for:

- Requirement gathering, propose solution and discuss with AWT MIS department
- Software development

With focus on feature enhancements, database management, debugging and maintaining the system. Front-end using C#.NET; Back-end using MS SQL stored procedures and functions

Support end users

Which included formal training sessions for introduction and effective use of new features in the software as well as handling queries from different users on daily basis.

Notable achievements in AWT web-application project:

- System generated Receipts, Transfer Letter, Recovery Letters and SMSs
- Security and Access management using password encryption and limiting rights of different users
- Feature to represent deposits in real-time, Save/upload photo, Change password etc.

Besides AWT web-application I was also involved in AWT Member Portal development. We were a team of two developers working under supervision of the Project manager.

While working at AWT, I formally presented AWT realestate dashboard to the management. It represents bulk information in graphs and charts. Similarly, I was involved in the training of AWT Office Automation System. This project promoted a paper free environment and quick process of minute-sheets and official letters. I also contributed in AWT realestate website content and assisted Marketing Department in the process.

Education

Folkuniversitetet

Korta vägen via Folkuniversitetet för utländska akademiker · (November 2022 - May 2023)

Lexicon Yrkesutbildning

Arbetsmarknadsutbildning, Programmering .NET · (September 2021 - March 2022)

COMSATS Institute of Information and Technology
Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Computer Engineering (2009 - 2013)